Today I will build my brand
day fifteen
You really got me now?
If things don't happen so much,
then the guy starts to think,
analyze a little bit of what's going wrong and insists until it works.
I need to create a brand to make me more interesting and less interested.
Dude start getting the salesman audio off my forehead.
You know,
but for that first I need to think of a name and a logo to make this happen.
No one goes out on the street wanting to buy anything.
The crowd buys it because it generated a connection.
And that's what I need to do from now on.
If you call.
First step crazy.
I set up an Instagram
iro mano ha ha I'll think of the slogan and get a lot of value
here now on this Instagram isn't an asshole either.
To start your business,
go to Canva for free and do a login,
what matters most is the way you tell your story to generate
value not in the product but in the experience.
And yesterday I invested 200reals in the craziest
idea I could have on this series.
But I'm waiting to get ready Man and as soon as I'm ready I believe I have
1 Instagram and it will make a lot more sense with my business.
until tomorrow.
Always wanna be by your side.